Guide to the Radio TV Reports Infomercial Collection, 1990-1996 RL.01062
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Original Tapes, 1990-1996; 1
  - Tape 179 - L,I, Medical Associates, WWOR-TV, 1994 Jan 29, 7:30 AM; Sandals Resort,WCBS, 1994 Feb 5, 1:30 AM; Dura Lube, TNN, 1994 Feb 5, 8:29 AM; 60-Second Grill Express, WWOR-TV, 1994 Feb 12, 8:00 AM., 1994-01-29/1994-02-12; 171
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 6, Video-cassette RL01062-VHS-0021)
  - Tape 180 - Royal Diamond Cookware, WWOR-TV, 1994 Feb 19, 9:00 AM; MDR Fitness Tabs, Lifetime, 1994 Feb 23, 2:00 PM; Driveway Detailer, Lifetime, 1994 Mar 11, 3:00 AM; The Home Right Painting, Family Channel, 1994 Mar 11, 2:30 AM., 1994-02-19/1994-03-11; 172
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 6, Video-cassette RL01062-VHS-0022)
  - Tape 181 - Barbie Classic Collection, Lifetime, 1994 Mar 13, 8:00 AM; Health Rider, Lifetime, 1994 Mar 13, 1:00 AM; Nu Hart Hair Product, Lifetime, 1994 Mar 13, 3:00 AM; Fidelity Investment, KCRA, 1994 May 15, 12:00 PM., 1994-03-13/1994-05-15; 173
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 6, Video-cassette RL01062-VHS-0023)
  - Tape 182 - Texaco Clean System Gasoline, WNBC-TV, 1994 Mar 19, 1:30 PM; Power Walk Plus, WWOR-TV, 1994 Mar 19, 9:00 AM; Fiberspeed 2000 Golf Shafts, WWOR-TV, 1994 Mar 19, 9:30 AM; Best Little Whorehouse in Texas, WPIX-TV, 1994 Mar 26, 8:00 AM., 1994-03-19/1994-03-26; 174
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 6, Video-cassette RL01062-VHS-0024)
  - Tape 183 - Smart Mop, WWOR-TV, 1994 Mar 26, 7:00 AM; American Lecture Series Library, WNYW-TV, 1994 Mar 27, 11:00 AM; Homeright Painting, WWOR-TV, 1994 Apr 9, 7:30 AM; The Wireless Wonder, WNBC-TV, 1994 Apr 16, 5:00 AM., 1994-03-26/1994-04-16; 175
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 6, Video-cassette RL01062-VHS-0025)
  - Tape 184 - The Wireless Wonder, WNBC-TV, 1994 Apr 16, 5:00 AM; Home Furnishings Company, WNBC-TV, 1994 Apr 17, 6:05 AM; Juiceman Juicer, Family Channel, 1994 Apr 28, 4:00 AM; Maxmusic Program, ETV, 1994 Apr 28, 3:00 AM., 1994-04-16/1994-04-28; 176
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 6, Video-cassette RL01062-VHS-0026)
  - Tape 185 - Medicus Pro, WWOR-TV, 1994 May 7, 7:00 AM; Time Life Sounds of the 70s, VH1, 1994 May 13, 4:00 AM; Earth Preservation, WTBS, 1994 May 8, 3:30 AM; Power Driver Screwdriver, WTBS, 1994 May 8, 4:00 AM., 1994-05-07/1994-05-13; 177
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 6, Video-cassette RL01062-VHS-0027)
  - Tape 186 - Health 2000, KNSD, 1994 Mar 31, 9:00 PM; Hoover Wet/Dry Vacuum, WGBO-TV, 1994 May 28, 9:30 AM; Kohler PDTS, WEWS, 1994 June 28, 2:46 AM; Fixodent Denture Adhesive, WVIT, 1994 July 9, 12:30 PM., 1994-03-31/1994-07-09; 178
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 6, Video-cassette RL01062-VHS-0028)
  - Tape 187 - Acne Statin, VH1, 1994 May 5, 4:00 AM; Jojo's Psychic Alliance, VH1, 1994 May 17, 4:00 AM; Natural Trim, WPIX-TV, 1994 May 14, 7:00 AM; Kurtain Kraft European, Lifetime, 1994 May 8, 8:00 AM., 1994-05-05/1994-05-17; 179
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 6, Video-cassette RL01062-VHS-0029)
  - Tape 188 - Health Rider, WNYW-TV, 1994 May 22, 11:30 AM; Buns of Steel, WWOR-TV, 1994 May 28, 8:30 AM; Pyromid Outdoor Cooking, Discovery, 1994 May 28, 3:30 AM; Denise Austin's Tone Up, WWOR-TV, 1994 June 11, 9:30 AM., 1994-05-22/1994-06-11; 180
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 6, Video-cassette RL01062-VHS-0030)
  - Tape 189 - E-Z Mop, WPIX-TV, 1994 June 4, 7:30 AM; Slick 50 Automotive Lubricant, TNN, 1994 July 9, 8:00 AM; Rio Hair, WCBS, 1994 July 9, 3:30 PM; Nucelle, Lifetime, 1994 May 16, 5:00 AM., 1994-05-16/1994-07-09; 181
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 7, Video-cassette Tape 189)
  - Tape 190 - X-1R Friction Eliminator, Comedy Central, 1994 May 2, 5:30 AM; Secrets of Making Love, Comedy Central, 1994 May 2, 4:30 AM; Bio Slim Weight Loss, Comedy Central, 1994 May 10, 5:30 AM; Time Life Sounds of the 70s, Lifetime, 1994 May 16, 5:30 AM., 1994-05-02/1994-05-16; 182
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 7, Video-cassette Tape 190)
  - Tape 191 - Desert Beauty Time, Lifetime, 1994 Feb 27, 9:00 AM; HBO Home Box Office, BET, 1994 June 18, 6:30 PM; Murad Most Beautiful, WWOR-TV, 1994 July 2, 8:30 AM; Roland Martin's Helicopter Lure, WWOR-TV, No date, No time., 1994-02-27/1994-07-02; 183
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 7, Video-cassette Tape 191)
  - Tape 192 - Quick 'n Brite, WGBO-TV, 1994 Aug 9, 6:00 AM; Kohler PDTS, KTVI, 1994 June 28, 2:40 PM; Alien Golf Club, WBBM, 1994 Aug 28, 12:00 PM; Life Fitness Exerciser, Comedy Central, 1994 July 20, 5:00 AM., 1994-06-28/1994-08-28; 184
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 7, Video-cassette Tape 192)
  - Tape 193 - Passion Profit and Power, WWOR-TV, 1994 June 18, 9:30 AM; Hip and Thigh Machine, USA, 1994 Mar 14, 3:30 AM; Super Slicer, Comedy Central, 1994 July 20, 4:30 AM; Memory Power Home Study, WNBC-TV, 1994 July 25, 2:38 AM., 1994-06-18/1994-07-25; 185
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 7, Video-cassette Tape 193)
  - Tape 194 - Alien Golf Club, WPIX-TV, 1994 Sep 3, 8:30 AM; Perfect Smile, WWOR-TV, 1994 Sep 3, 10:30 AM; Remington's Soundmate, WWOR-TV, 1994 Sep 10, 10:00 AM; Microbuddy Microwave, WCBS, 1994 Sep 24, 2:30 PM., 1994-09-03/1994-09-24; 186
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 7, Video-cassette Tape 194)
  - Tape 195 - Tony Little Ab Isolator, WWOR-TV, 1994 Oct 8, 11:00 AM; Inteliquest, CNBC, 1994 Oct 4, 3:30 AM; American Business, WCBS, 1994 Oct 8, 1:30 PM; HBO Home Box Office, BET, 1994 June 18, 6:30 PM., 1994-06-18/1994-10-08; 187
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 7, Video-cassette Tape 195)
  - Tape 196 - Toyota Motor Sales, WCBS, 1994 Nov 5, 2:00 PM; Tops Appliance City, WPIX-TV, 1994 Nov 4, 12:20 AM; Magnavox PDTS, WWOR-TV, 1994 Nov 5, 8:30 AM; Body by Jake Ab and Back,WWOR-TV, 1994 Nov 5, 10:00 AM., 1994-11-04/1994-11-05; 188
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 7, Video-cassette Tape 196)
  - Tape 197 - Hidden Keys, WPIX-TV, 1994 July 30, 8:00 AM; Vitapower, Comedy Central, 1994 Sep 1, 5:00 AM; Fisher Appliances, WCBS, 1994 Oct 30, 2:00 PM; The Clinton Chronicles, WWOR-TV, 1994 Oct 29, 8:30 AM., 1994-07-30/1994-10-30; 189
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 7, Video-cassette Tape 197)
  - Tape 198 - Perfect Hair System, WCBS, 1994 Nov 12, 2:00 PM; Bissell Plus Vacuum, WWOR-TV, 1994 Nov 26, 10:00 AM; Power Foam Carpet Cleaner, WNBC-TV, 1994 Nov 22, 3:06 AM; Better Blocks, Discovery, 1994 Nov 14, 8:00 AM., 1994-11-12/1994-11-26; 190
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 7, Video-cassette Tape 198)
  - Tape 199 - Tone Up 1 2 3, Lifetime, 1994 Dec 1, 2:30 PM; Luxurious Hair Extensions, Lifetime, 1994 Dec 1, 4:30 PM; Apple PDTS Computer, WABC, 1994 Dec 2, 5:30 AM; The Nativity Cross, WWOR-TV, 1994 Dec 3, 10:30 AM., 1994-12-01/1994-12-03; 191
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 7, Video-cassette Tape 199)
  - Tape 200 - Fortunoff the Source, WPIX-TV, 1994 Nov 26, 8:30 AM; Bissell Plus Vacuum, WWOR-TV, 1994 Nov 26, 10:00 AM; Sega CD, WCBS, 1994 Nov 25, 2:05 AM; Nowet Wonder Foam Cleaner, WWOR-TV, 1994 Dec 24, 8:30 AM., 1994-11-25/1994-12-24; 192
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 7, Video-cassette Tape 200)
  - Tape 201 - Purina Pet Dry Dog Food, WNYW-TV, 1994 Nov 4, 10:38 AM; Secret Hair Program, Lifetime, 1994 Aug 31, 3:30 AM; Target Discount Program, WPWR, 1994 Nov 26, 9:00 AM; Geo Safari, WWOR-TV, 1995 Jan 7, 10:30 AM., 1994-08-31/1995-01-07; 193
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 7, Video-cassette Tape 201)
  - Tape 202 - Bosley Medical Institute, NBC, 1995 Jan 22, 1:32 PM; Travel Perks, WWOR-TV, 1995 Jan 21, 10:30 AM; Quick 'n Brite, WWOR-TV, 1995 Jan 21, 11:30 AM; National Home Business, WPIX-TV, 1995 Jan 21, 7:30 AM., 1995-01-21/1995-01-22; 194
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 7, Video-cassette Tape 202)
  - Tape 203 - Berland's House of Tools, WGBO-TV, 1994 Nov 26, 8:30 AM; Chevrolet Trucks, WBBM, 1994 Nov 26, 5:10 AM; Tony Little Videos, WLS, 1994 June 18, 10:00 AM; U,S, Healthcare Medical Insurance, CBS, 1994 Nov 26, 1:00 PM., 1994-06-18/1994-11-26; 195
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 7, Video-cassette Tape 203)
  - Tape 204 - Power Driver Screwdriver, TNN, 1995 Jan 1, 8:00 AM; Financial Freedom, WNBC-TV, 1995 Jan 9, 2:37 AM; Braun PDTS Hand Blender, WWOR-TV, 1995 Jan 7, 9:30 AM; Fast Track Exerciser, WWOR-TV, 1994 Nov 26, 8:00 AM., 1994-11-26/1995-01-09; 196
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 7, Video-cassette Tape 204)
  - Tape 205 - Braun PDTS Oral B Plaque Remover, WWOR-TV, 1995 Jan 28, 9:30 AM; National Strategic Alliance, WPIX-TV, 1995 Jan 28, 7:30 AM; Money Makers Live Program, WNBC-TV, 1995 Jan 28, 5:00 AM; Circuit City, WLS, 1995 Jan 29, 11:30 AM., 1995-01-28/1995-01-29; 197
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 7, Video-cassette Tape 205)
  - Tape 206 - New Hair Institute, WNBC-TV, 1995 Feb 4, 3:30 AM; Pasta Express, WABC, 1995 Feb 4, 4:00 AM; Bread Classic 2000, WCBS, 1995 Feb 4, 5:30 AM; E-Force, WWOR-TV, 1995 Feb 4, 9:00 AM., 1995-02-04; 198
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 7, Video-cassette Tape 206)
  - Tape 207 - Kitchen Wizard, WNBC-TV, 1995 Feb 20, 3:06 AM; Dual-Action Acne Regimen, WWOR-TV, 1995 Feb 11, 7:30 AM; Abflex Exerciser, WWOR-TV, 1995 Feb 18, 8:30 AM; T Touch Pet Training, WABC, 1995 Feb 25, 4:00 AM., 1995-02-11/1995-02-25; 199
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 7, Video-cassette Tape 207)
  - Tape 208 - Charles J, Givens, WPIX-TV, 1995 Mar 4, 7:30 AM; Roly Kit Organizer, WPIX-TV, 1995 Mar 4, 8:30 AM; Smart Chopper, WWOR-TV, 1995 Mar 4, 10:30 AM; Sonicare Toothbrush, CNBC, 1995 Mar 5, 3:00 PM., 1995-03-04/1995-03-05; 200
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 7, Video-cassette Tape 208)
  - Tape 209 - Dance Mix USA '95, WNBC-TV, 1995 Mar 7, 3:06 AM; Touchless Instant Restoration, WWOR-TV, 1995 Feb 25, 7:00 AM; Walkfit, WWOR-TV, 1995 Feb 25, 10:30 AM; Farewell to Fat, WWOR-TV, 1995 Feb 25, 11:30 AM., 1995-02-25/1995-03-07; 201
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 7, Video-cassette Tape 209)
  - Tape 210 - Realm Fragrances Men's and Women's, Sci-Fi, 1995 Mar 22, 3:30 AM; Face-Fit Facial Exerciser, Sci-Fi, 1995 Mar 22, 4:30 AM; Third Federal Savings and Loan, WEWS, 1995 Feb 12, 1:00 PM; Principal Secrets--Victoria Principal, Comedy Central, 1995 Jan 23, 7:30 AM., 1995-01-23/1995-03-22; 202
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 7, Video-cassette Tape 210)
  - Tape 211 - Powertrainer Exercise Machine, Comedy Central, 1995 Mar 20, 7:00 AM; The Wholesale Buying Guide, Lifetime, 1995 Mar 21, 7:00 AM; Better Blocks, WTTE, 1994 Dec 21, 11:19 PM; Bosley Medical Institute, USA, 1995 Jan 22, 4:30 AM., 1994-12-21/1995-03-20; 203
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 7, Video-cassette Tape 211)
  - Tape 212 - Attacking Anxiety II, WWOR-TV, 1995 Apr 1, 8:00 AM; Ez-Chopper, WWOR-TV, 1995 Apr 8, 11:30 AM; Time Life Dick Clark, ETV, 1995 Mar 23, 3:30 AM; Sony PDTS Minidisc, CNBC, 1995 Apr 2, 10:30 AM., 1995-03-23/1995-04-08; 204
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 7, Video-cassette Tape 212)
  - Tape 213 - Where There Is a Will There Is an A--John Ritter, Lifetime, 1995 Mar 22, 7:00 AM; Infomercial Making, CBS, 1995 Apr 8, 2:58 PM; K-Tel 101 Greatest,Comedy Central, 1995 Apr 20, 5:30 AM; Five Attractions, WPIX-TV, 1994 June 18, 8:30 AM., 1994-06-18/1995-04-20; 205
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 7, Video-cassette Tape 213)
  - Tape 214 - Lesko's Info, WABC, 1995 Apr 30, 6:00 AM; Sophist-O-Twist Hair, WWOR-TV, 1995 Apr 29, 9:30 AM; San Antonio Promotion, Lifetime, 1995 Apr 25, 7:00 AM; Health Rider, WWOR-TV, 1995 May 6, 10:00 AM., 1995-04-25/1995-06-06; 206
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 7, Video-cassette Tape 214)
  - Tape 215 - Mathemagics, WCBS, 1995 May 27, 2:00 PM; Psychic Friends Network, WWOR-TV, 1995 May 20, 7:00 AM; Five Attractions, WPIX-TV, 1994 June 18, 8:30 AM; Autobike Classic, TNN, 1995 May 28, 8:00 AM., 1994-06-18/1995-05-28; 207
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 7, Video-cassette Tape 215)
  - Tape 216 - Feed the Children, WNBC-TV, 1995 May 10, 2:38 AM; Home Right Painting, WWOR-TV, 1995 May 13, 9:30 AM; Nature Sleep Mattress, CNBC, 1995 May 11, 3:30 AM; Champions of Entrepreneurs, WNBC-TV, 1995 May 8, 2:38 AM., 1995-05-08/1995-05-13; 208
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 7, Video-cassette Tape 216)
  - Tape 217 - Pedigree Pet Foods, CNBC, 1995 June 23, 4:00 PM; Victoria Jackson, WNBC-TV, 1995 June 3, 1:30 PM; Golfsmith Golf Club, CNBC, 1995 May 20, 2:00 PM; Making Life Easier, WWOR-TV, 1995 June 10, 8:00 AM., 1995-05-20/1995-06-23; 209
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 7, Video-cassette Tape 217)
  - Tape 218 - Durashine Advanced Auto Polish, WNBC-TV, 1995 May 20, 3:30 AM; AT&T, WCIX, 1995 June 25, 11:30 AM; Tempo Trainer 911, SPCH, 1995 June 7, 9:30 AM; Playboy Magazine, Comedy Central, 1995 June 19, 9:30 AM., 1995-05-20/1995-06-25; 210
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 7, Video-cassette Tape 218)
  - Tape 219 - The Compact Chair, WWOR-TV, 1995 June 17, 10:30 AM; Eagle Eyes, WWOR-TV, 1995 June 17, 8:00 AM; Magnavox CD-1 System, WNYW-TV, 1995 June 18, 11:30 AM; Sears Kenmore Hepa, Lifetime, 1995 June 20, 7:00 AM., 1995-06-17/1995-06-20; 211
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 8, Video-cassette Tape 219)
  - Tape 220 - Rogaine Hair Treatment, Lifetime, 1995 June 28, 7:00 AM; Home Business Network, WPIX-TV, 1995 June 24, 8:30 AM; Lexus Certified Pre-Owned Automobiles, WABC, 1995 July 8, 1:00 PM; Food Dehydrator, KASN, 1995 July 3, 10:30 AM., 1995-06-24/1995-07-08; 212
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 8, Video-cassette Tape 220)
  - Tape 221 - Hy G Ionic Toothbrush, TNN, 1995 July 15, 8:00 AM; Mathemagics, BET, 1995 July 15, 11:00 PM; Chrysler Plymouth Dealers, WPIX-TV, 1995 July 15, 6:15 PM; AT&T, WNYW-TV, 1995 July 16, 11:00 AM., 1995-07-15/1995-07-16; 213
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 8, Video-cassette Tape 221)
  - Tape 222 - American Business, WPIX-TV, 1995 Aug 5, 6:00 AM; Natural Cover Make-Up, TVFN, 1995 Aug 16, 5:30 AM; Remembering the 80s, WWOR-TV, 1995 Aug 20, 1:00 AM; Aspen Wellness Group, WCBS, 1995 Aug 19, 2:00 PM., 1995-08-05/1995-08-20; 214
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 8, Video-cassette Tape 222)
  - Tape 223 - Pedigree Pet Foods, CNBC, 1995 Apr 23, 4:00PM; Bosley Medical Institute, NBC, 1995 Aug 24, 2:42 AM; Stilson & Stilson, NBC, 1995 Aug 24, 8:11 AM; RCA Digital Satellite, WPIX-TV, 1995 Aug 26, 7:00 AM., 1995-04-23/1995-08-26; 215
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 8, Video-cassette Tape 223)
  - Tape 224 - Microsoft Windows, WNBC-TV, 1995 Aug 27, 3:30 PM; Sweepa Rubber Broom, WWOR-TV, 1995 Sep 30, 10:30 AM; Thermoscan, WABC, 1995 Oct 20, 4:00 AM; Lightolier, WWOR-TV, 1995 Oct 21, 7:30 AM., 1995-08-27/1995-10-21; 216
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 8, Video-cassette Tape 224)
  - Tape 225 - Cholestaway Dietary Supplement, Discovery, 1995 Sep 23, 8:00 AM; Command Performance, WNBC-TV, 1995 Oct 9, 2:37 AM; New Jersey Education Association, WWOR-TV, 1995 Sep 30, 7:30 AM; Sweepa Rubber Broom, WWOR-TV, 1995 Sep 30, 10:30 AM., 1995-09-30/1995-10-09; 217
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 8, Video-cassette Tape 225)
  - Tape 226 - Proactiv Solution, Lifetime, 1995 Sep 18, 2:00 AM; Total Body Power, Lifetime, 1995 Sep 18, 2:30 AM; Chroma Trim Gum, WNBC-TV, 1995 Sep 9, 5:30 AM; QRB Ultimate Cleaner, WABC, 1995 Aug 27, 6:00 AM., 1995-08-27/1995-09-18; 218
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 8, Video-cassette Tape 226)
  - Tape 227 - New Jersey Education Association, WWOR-TV, 1995 Sep 16, 7:30 AM; Metrinch tools, CNBC, 1995 Sep 10, 3:00 AM; MGM/UA Home Movies, WWOR-TV, 1995 Oct 7, 11:30 AM; New Jersey Education Association, WWOR-TV, 1995 Oct 14, 7:30 AM., 1995-09-10/1995-10-14; 219
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 8, Video-cassette Tape 227)
  - Tape 228 - Hydron Skin Care, WWOR-TV, 1995 Oct 21, 8:30 AM; Fast Track Exerciser, WNYW-TV, 1995 Oct 29, 9:30 AM; United Home Karaoke, WNBC-TV, 1995 Oct 28, 4:00 AM; Quicksilver Cleaning, WWOR-TV, 1995 Oct 28, 8:30 AM., 1995-10-21/1995-10-29; 220
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 8, Video-cassette Tape 228)
  - Tape 229 - EZ Krunch Exerciser, WWOR-TV, 1995 Oct 28, 11:00 AM; Bee Alive Royal Jelly, KWHB, 1995 Oct 18, 1:30 PM; Power Walk Plus, WWOR-TV, 1995 Nov 4, 9:00 AM; Total Body Comfort, WWOR-TV, 1995 Nov 4, 10:00 AM., 1995-10-18/1995-11-04; 221
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 8, Video-cassette Tape 229)
  - Tape 230 - Contemporary Collectibles, Lifetime, 1995 Oct 8, 7:00 AM; Oxford Health Plans, WCBS, 1995 Oct 14, 2:30 PM; Troy-Bilt Chipper, WABC, 1995 Oct 14, 5:30 AM; Wonder Cooker, WABC, 1995 Oct 15, 6:00 AM., 1995-10-08/1995-10-15; 222
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 8, Video-cassette Tape 230)
  - Tape 231 - New Jersey Education Association, WWOR-TV, 1995 Nov 25, 7:30 AM; Oxford Health Plans, WCBS, 1995 Oct 14, 2:30 PM; Sega Pico Interactive, WWOR-TV, 1995 Nov 11, 11:00 AM; Lean Mean Fat Reducing, WNBC-TV, 1995 Dec 11, 2:38 AM., 1995-10-14/1995-12-11; 223
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 8, Video-cassette Tape 231)
  - Tape 232 - Ab Roller Plus, WWOR-TV, 1995 Nov 11, 7:00 AM; New Jersey Education Association, WWOR-TV, 1995 Nov 11, 7:30 AM; Bowdazzler, WCBS, 1995 Nov 12, 3:00 PM; Perfect Equation, WWOR-TV, 1995 Nov 18, 8:00 AM., 1995-11-11/1995-11-18; 224
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 8, Video-cassette Tape 232)
  - Tape 233 - Mega System, WWOR-TV, 1995 Dec 2, 10:30 AM; Years Away Beauty Lifts, WNBC-TV, 1995 May 13, 4:30 AM; Electronic Cop Security, WABC, 1995 Dec 3, 6:00 AM; 1-800-Flowers Florists, ABC, 1995 Dec 8, 6:00 AM., 1995-05-13/1995-12-08; 225
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 8, Video-cassette Tape 233)
  - Tape 234 - New Jersey Education Association, WWOR-TV, 1995 Dec 9, 7:30 AM; Sony Instant Surround Sound System, WWOR-TV, 1995 Dec 9, 11:30 AM; Food Dehydrator, WNYW-TV, 1995 Dec 17, 9:30 AM; Magnavox Home Security, Comedy Central, 1995 Nov 19, 5:00 AM., 1995-11-19/1995-12-17; 226
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 8, Video-cassette Tape 234)
  - Tape 335 - Ab Trainer, Sci-Fi, 1995 Dec 31, 8:30 AM; Health Rider, WWOR-TV, 1995 Dec 30, 8:00 AM; Hydron Skin Care, WWOR-TV, 1995 Oct 21, 8:30 AM; Cardioglide, WNBC-TV, 1994 Nov 15, 3:06 AM., 1994-11-15/1995-12-31; 227
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 8, Video-cassette Tape 335)
  - Tape 336 - Diabetes Watch, KPIX, 1995 July 22, 6:30 PM; Century 21 Real Estate, WJW, 1995 Nov 19, 10:09 AM; Elek-Tek Computer Store, HCNB, 1995 Nov 18, 11:00 AM; For Women Only, WTTE, 1996 Jan 22, 11:30 AM., 1995-07-22/1996-01-22; 228
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 8, Video-cassette Tape 336)
  - Tape 337 - Poetic Return of Pablo Neruda, WNYW-TV, 1996 Jan 7, 9:30 AM; Joe Montana's Contour Cross, WWOR-TV, 1996 Jan 6, 10:30 AM; Mon Amie Cosmetics, WWOR-TV, 1996 Jan 13, 6:39 PM; American Home Business, NBC, 1996 Jan 10, 3:06 AM., 1996-01-06/1996-01-13; 229
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 8, Video-cassette Tape 337)
  - Tape 338 - New Media Calling, WWOR-TV, 1996 Jan 27, 1:30 AM; Don Lapre Making Money Package, ETV, 1996 Feb 9, 4:00 AM; Golden Opportunity Jewelry, Family Channel, 1996 Feb 8, 4:00 AM; Universal Seminars, NBC, 1996 Jan 12, 2:37 AM., 1996-01-12/1996-02-09; 230
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 8, Video-cassette Tape 338)
  - Tape 339 - Assist, CNN, 1996 Jan 25, 11:58 PM; Looney Tunes, Lifetime, 1996 Jan 24, 1:11 PM; Years Away Beauty Lifts, WNBC-TV, 1996 Feb 8, 2:38 AM., 1996-01-24/1996-02-08; 231
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 8, Video-cassette Tape 339)
  - Tape 340 - Cholestaway Dietary Supplement, WWOR-TV, 1996, No time; Financial Concepts, WNYW-TV, 1996, No time; The Book of Mormon, AT, 1996, No time; Aroma-Trim, CNBC, 1996, No time., 232
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 8, Video-cassette Tape 340)
  - Tape 341 - Carleton Sheets, CNBC, 1996 Feb 13, 3:00 AM; Waltham Formula Canned and Dry Dog Food, WNBC-TV, 1996 Feb 13, 3:06 AM; Mon Amie Cosmetics, CNBC, 1996 Feb 12, 4:30 AM; Years Away Beauty Lifts, WNBC-TV, 1996 Feb 8, 2:38 AM., 1996-02-08/1996-02-13; 233
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 8, Video-cassette Tape 341)
  - Tape 342 - Black Magic Spray N Wax, TNN, 1996 Mar 10, 4:30 AM; Water Processor, WTBS, 1996 Feb 19, 3:30 AM; Secrets to Making Money, Comedy Central, 1996 Feb 15, 4:00 AM; Money Makers Live Program, Comedy Central, 1996 Feb 15, 4:30 AM., 1996-02-15/1996-03-10; 234
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 8, Video-cassette Tape 342)
  - Tape 343 - Prolong Super Lubricants, Speed Channel, 1996 Mar 16, 7:30 AM; New Jersey Education Association, WWOR-TV, 1996 Mar 16, 7:30 AM; Denise Austin's Complete Workout, WWOR-TV, 1996 Mar 9, 7:30 AM; Motor Up Additive, TNN, 1996 Mar 16, 8:00 AM., 1996-03-09/1996-03-16; 235
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 8, Video-cassette Tape 343)
  - Tape 344 - Health Rider, WWOR-TV, 1995 Dec 30, 8:00 AM; Chiropractic Centennial, WWOR-TV, 1996 Mar 2, 10:00 AM; Universal Seminars, NBC, 1996 Jan 12, 2:37 AM., 1995-12-30/1996-03-02; 236
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 8, Video-cassette Tape 344)
  - Tape 345 - Success and You, WNBC-TV, 1996 Apr 1, 2:37 AM; Secrets to Making Money, Sci-Fi, 1996 Mar 24, 8:31 AM; Lubricator 2000 Super, WWOR-TV, 1996 Apr 6, 8:00 AM; Ruth Prodan's Burner, CNBC, 1996 Apr 1, 3:30 AM., 1996-03-24/1996-04-06; 237
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 8, Video-cassette Tape 345)
  - Tape 346 - New Jersey Education Association, WWOR-TV, 1996 Apr 27, 7:30 AM; Pilates Performer, Lifetime, 1996 Apr 26, 7:00 AM; Computer Personalities, TNN, 1996 May 4, 8:00 AM., 1996-04-26/1996-05-04; 238
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 8, Video-cassette Tape 346)
  - Tape 347 - Nutrivida Vitamins, WNJU, 1996 June 1, 2:30 PM; Hoover Dirt Finder Vacuum, WDIV, 1996 May 25, 4:30 PM; Aroma-Trim, WTTV, 1996 Mar 22, 9:31 AM; Cardio Walk Exerciser, WCIU, 1996 Feb 10, 9:00 AM., 1996-02-10/1996-06-01; 239
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 8, Video-cassette Tape 347)
  - Tape 348 - Zoom Personal Styling Salon, Lifetime, 1996 May 13, 7:00 AM; Nobody Beats the Wiz, MSG, 1996 May 15, 8:42 AM; Smart Walk Triple Action Treadmill, Discovery, 1996 May 16, 5:00 AM; Team Jenner Winning Formula, WWOR-TV, 1996 May 18, 7:00 AM., 1996-05-13/1996-05-18; 240
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 8, Video-cassette Tape 348)
  - Tape 349 - Perfect Abs, WWOR-TV, 1996 May 19, 7:00 AM; Team Jenner Winning Formula, WWOR-TV, 1996 May 18, 7:00 AM; Secrets of Success, WWOR-TV, 1996 May 20, 7:30 AM; New Jersey Education Association, WWOR-TV, 1996 May 25, 7:30 AM., 1996-05-18/1996-05-25; 241
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 9, Video-cassette Tape 349)
  - Tape 350 - Power Wash, WWOR-TV, 1996 May 25, 9:30 AM; Hidden Keys to Loving Relationships, Lifetime, 1996 May 28, 7:00 AM; Larouche for President, WNYW-TV, 1996 June 2, 9:30 AM; Time Life Recording, Lifetime, 1996 June 12, 7:00 AM., 1996-05-25/1996-06-12; 242
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 9, Video-cassette Tape 350)
  - Tape 352 - Magikan Trashcan, WWOR-TV, 1996, No time; Sweet Simplicity, Lifetime, 1996, No time; Bee Alive Royal Jelly, WWOR-TV, 1996, No time; Smooth & Natural Facial, WWOR-TV, 1996, No time., 243
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 9, Video-cassette Tape 352)
  - Tape 353 - Barbie My Fair Lady Collection, Lifetime, 1996No time; Co-Eds, WWOR-TV, 1996, No time; Ever Last, CBS, 1996No time; Ab Shaper, WWOR-TV, 1996, No time., 244
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 9, Video-cassette Tape 353)
  - Tape 354 - Tony Little's Abs, WWOR-TV, 1996 Aug 8, 8:30 AM; World Business, WWOR-TV, 1996 Aug 10, 7:00 AM; MGM/UA Presents Pee-Wee, WWOR-TV, 1996 Aug 10, 8:30 AM., 1996-08-08/1996-08-10; 245
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 9, Video-cassette Tape 354)